gpnotebook.co.uk 2019-06-15

# General Practice Notebook

This website is provided by Oxbridge Solutions Limited, registered in England and Wales under company number 2592842 at Ground Floor, 108 Cannon Street, London, EC4N 6EU, UK.  
We take very seriously the privacy of our website users and the security of their personal information.   
This Privacy Policy together with our Terms and Conditions (<http://www.gpnotebook.co.uk/TnC.cfm>) set out the principles governing our use of personal information which you give or we obtain about you. By using this website you agree to this use. We ask you to read this Privacy Policy carefully. Any dispute which may arise over privacy will be subject to this policy, any data collection notice incorporated into this website and the provisions of English law.   
We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. Therefore we ask you to check this Privacy Policy occasionally to ensure that you are aware of the most recent version which will apply each time you access this website. 

DESCRIPTION OF THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

**Personal Information**  
If you have filled in a registration form either on this or a third party site then we will collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, e-mail address, country of residence and other information which you voluntarily submit. If you contact us we may keep a record of that correspondence. We may also collect information about how you in particular use this website through the use of cookies (see below).   
When you submit personal information you consent to our use of the information as set out in this Privacy Policy.   
This information helps us to personalise your experience by tailoring the content you see, optimising your enjoyment of the website.   
We may also obtain information about your opinions if, for example, you send us feedback, or ask us questions.   
We may also, occasionally, receive information about you from other sources (such as third parties or associated sites) which we will add to the information which we already hold about you in order to help us improve and personalise our service to you.   
We use Google Analytics tracking to track user activity. The data we collect about users in Google Analytics can be connected to other data we have about the end user, as per the measurement policy supplied by Google. We will not upload any data that allows Google to personally identify an individual (such as certain names, Social Security Numbers, email addresses, or any similar data), or data that permanently identifies a particular device (such as a unique device identifier if such an identifier cannot be reset)

**Use of Cookies**  
In common with many organisations we monitor the use of this website by collecting aggregate information through the use of cookies. No personally identifiable data are collected in this process. Typically, we collect information about the number of visitors to the website, to each web page and the originating domain name of the visitor's Internet Service Provider. This information helps us to improve our site and to deliver a more personalised service and may be shared with third parties.   
A cookie is a small file which is placed on your computer's hard drive. The file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.  
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.  
Some of our advertising banners may send a cookie to your hard disk (whether or not you click the banner). If you subsequently visit the advertised website we will know that you have seen our banner. This allows us to keep track of the success rates of such banners.   
The majority of web browsers accept cookies, but you can usually change the web browser’s settings to refuse new cookies, disable existing ones or simply let you know when new ones are sent to your hard disk. However, please be aware that, if you refuse or disable cookies, some of the website’s functionality may be lost. To learn more about how to refuse or disable cookies please visit “aboutcookies.org”. 

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We may use your personal information to (a) verify your healthcare professional status, (b) provide you with information, products or services that you have requested from us or (c) carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us. Other purposes for which we may use your personal information may be disclosed to you when you provide your personal information.   
Where you indicate your consent, we may also provide you with helpful information and updates, notify you, where appropriate, of new gpnotebook services and seek your views on our products and services. 

WHO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH

We will keep your information confidential. We will not pass your information to anyone else without your consent, except for (a) successors in title to our business or (b) when required by law. Companies and individuals who provide services and functions on our behalf may also use and store your personal information. However they may not use your personal information for any other purpose.

We may also pass your information to business partners with whom we may jointly offer products or services. You can tell when a third party is involved in a product or service you have requested because their name will appear with ours. If you choose to access these optional services, we may share information about you, including your personal information, with those partners so that they can contact you directly by email or post about their products and services. Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these third-party business partners. 

OPTING OUT OF FURTHER COMMUNICATIONS FROM US

If we have specified (in a data collection notice on this website) that we will contact you with information about our products, services, or those of other companies and you wish to opt out of receiving such information, then you can do so by sending an e-mail to support@gpnotebook.co.uk. You should clearly state on all communications: your name, username (if any), registration details (if any) and the name of this website. You may also edit your contact preferences on your profile page.

HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

If we collect any information relating to you, we will store it on a secure server. We have in place security policies which are intended to ensure, as far as possible, the security and integrity of all our information, including your personal information. However, whilst we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site and any transmission is at your own risk. 

CHILDREN

Our website is directed at an adult audience of healthcare professionals. We do not knowingly collect information from or about children. 

IMPROPER CONDUCT 

We may use the information we gather and/or receive about you to investigate and help prevent unlawful activity or activity that threatens our network or otherwise jeopardises the provision of this website and we may disclose such information to third parties (such as the police) for these purposes. 

ACCESS AND CORRECTIONS 

If we process personal information about you, then you have a right under the Data Protection Act 1998 to request access to that personal information (for which we may charge a small fee).   
You also have a right to require any inaccuracies in your information to be corrected free of charge. You can ask us to modify your details by sending an e-mail to support@gpnotebook.co.uk or by post to:

The Data Controller  
Dr Damian C. Crowther  
18 Ross Street  
Cambridge  
CB1 3BX   
UK

Please state your name, username (if any), registration details (if any) and the name of this website clearly on all communications.
